CURRICULUM VITAE

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Name: Le Duc Thinh

Date of birth: January 20th, 1980

Telephone number: 0985 869 485

Email: <u>thinhld80@gmai.com</u>

Address 141/14/20 339 Street, Ward Phuoc Long B, District 9, Ho Chi Minh City

Nationality: Vietnamese

Sex: Male

Marital status: Married

Motivated, teamwork-oriented, and responsible Data Analyst with significant experience in increasing comprehension of reports and presentations by the average professional. Highly educated, possessing two Bachelors', a Master's. Good in English, with elementary understanding of German.

① 0985869485

TECHNICAL (IT) SKILLS

Data Database Design & Management, Data Quality Assessment, Data Analysis, Pattern

Management & Trend Identification, Visualization of Data Insights, Data Manipulation

Computer System Administration, Advanced Microsoft Excel Functions, Relational databases,

Science MS SQL Server, MySQL, R Studio, Python, C/C++, Java, Troubleshooting

Research Math, Statistics, Analysis, Problem solving, Quantitative Methods, Regression

analysis

WORK EXPERIENCE

Lecturer in IT Department

Ho Chi Minh City University of Transport

4/2008 - Present

- Teaching Essential Information Technology included MS Word, MS Excel, MS Power Point, problem solving methods in computer.

- Teaching Programming languages included Object oriented, data structure and algorithms,
 C/C++, Java, C#
- Homeroom teacher and studying consultant

Credit staff trainee

Dong A Bank

8/2010 - 10/2010

- Instructing business borrowers and receiving their loan applications
- Reviewing loan applications (borrowing purpose, repayment capacity, mortgaged assets)
- Determining the credit limit and submitting it to the manager for credit evaluation and approval
- Inspecting approved loan applications; reporting invalid and unqualified loan applications
- Evaluating operating profit, repayment capacity, financial market and market outlook to warn about the risk of loans.
- Coordinating with debt retirement staffs to handle overdue credits
- Reporting to Head of Credit Department

Lecturer in IT Department

Ho Chi Minh City University of Industry

4/2005 - 3/2007

- Teaching programming technique with Java
- Teaching Windows Form programming technique with C#

IT support executive

TPL COMPANY

3/2003 - 3/2005

- Install and configure computer systems, setting up new users, supporting new applications.
- Manage and assist in the maintenance of hardware and software.
- Providing database backup and recovery. Troubleshooting and performing database administration
- Being responsible for improvement and maintenance of the databases to include rollout, patching and upgrades.
- Meeting users to define and evaluate business problems; analyze detailed systems factors.
 Worked as an interface between the users and the different teams involved with application development to enhance understanding IT processes
- Worked under the general supervision of senior staff with some latitude for the exercise of independent judgment

EDUCATION

Masters in Corporate Finance

University of Economics Ho Chi Minh City 6/2015 – 1/2018

Bachelor of science in Mathematics and Computer Sciences

Ho Chi Minh City University of Natural Sciences 7/1998 – 2/2003

Bachelor of Banking and Finance

University of Economics Ho Chi Minh City 6/2007 – 10/2010

PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATES

Microsoft SQL Server certificate	CCNA certificate
Computer Science Center of Ho Chi Minh City	Nhat Nghe Computer Science Center
University of Natural Sciences	